who are these nobodies up here to make
fun of you you're an inspiration uh you
prove that having no talent can be seen
as hip and ironic you greasy greek
bastard we shouldn't be drilling in
alaska we should be ringing out your
family's pillowcases you used to look
your age now you don't even look your
species
[Applause]
lisa lampanelli keep it going for that
guy wasn't he funny
seriously
wasn't he hilarious i love the
the pink camouflage lisa you're like
general fatten
holy look at you you fat who
knew lane bryant's had an army
lisa actually has a lot in common with
that octo mom that woman that gave birth
all those babies she's never given birth
but she has had 80 fingers inside her at
the same time
look at this pack of slobs up here gary
busey's here kind of
how about gary
yeah
gary i guess flew in from lobotomy
island
jesus gary you horse-faced lunatic
you look like you look like nick nolte
the clydesdale
your teeth look like a row of urinals
look at yourself every time you talk i
want to piss in your
mouth and i don't uh
warren
what the hell are you doing here holy
warren was he was great on dancing
with the stars he came in second and
then celebrated by dragging his partner
to the top of the empire state building
it's great to see toby keith toby i'm
glad you could take time out from
spitting on mexicans to be here tobia
toby you put the big and bigot i loved
your last song get out of my country you
camel jockey spook jew
[Music]
and uh
marcia brady's here maureen mccormick
how about that holy marsha brady
you wrote in your book that used to
trade sex for drugs holy as a kid i
used to fantasize about having sex with
you who knew all i needed was an eight
ball and a bus station bathroom
and speaking of bathroom stalls where's
that redneck fruit jeff foxworthy
there he is
jeff you look like magnum p.i with aids
my buddy uh nick depaolo's here nick
look at you you big hunched over guinea
you're like fonzie with spina bifida
and reno collier i don't know who or
what that is i i i don't know
i guess he's part of that next wave of
low brow that'll make me want
to kill myself or or maybe he's just
here so lisa lampanelli wouldn't be the
only fat lesbian hack on stage
and now uh on to larry the cable guy
this this is exciting i got to tell you
i've never roasted a fake character
before maybe next year we can roast
spongebob squarepants
larry's
larry's whole act is a sham like the
bible or the holocaust
some people say larry's only successful
because he's pandering to the lowest
common denominator and blatantly and
non-ironically exploiting people's
racists and homophobic tendencies don't
listen to these people larry they're
just bitter and jealous and right
you inbred hillbilly you've been inside
more farm animals than purina
you're like the trojan army you're big
patriotic and you both came inside a
giant horse
you gravy sweating cousin
larry his first cousin when he
was 16 and his last one about an hour
ago
he lost 50 pounds on nutrisystem and
another 10 when you shaved your back
how the are you so popular
jesus christ this one finally
broke my back
your fans can't even afford cable
they're not coming because they think
you're funny they're just they've never
seen a cable guy you could have come up
with other characters your fans have
never seen like larry the dentist or
larry the librarian or larry the high
school diploma
thanks for letting me roast you uh larry
you you make more money in a week that
i'll make in my life and uh and that
feels good i gotta tell you you say
you've never done drugs but watching
your success has put me in rehab twice
so uh thanks for ripping my soul out you
hillbilly
donny osmond everybody wasn't she funny
what a boar holy
but you know what i do i do love that
that stewie character on your show he's
great uh you made all your money because
you created a
criminal baby you're like michael lohan
how uh
how
how how cheesy is this deus how cheesy
is this taste it's not a roast it's a
melt jerry springer george hamilton look
at these no talent success stories the
devil has signed so many deals with you
people he's got carpal tunnel
syndrome pam anderson he's here
everybody i hope this isn't too direct
pam but god i i've jerked off to you a
lot uh you you've caused me to spill
more seed than muhammad ali at a bird
feeder
pam you
you have uh
you
there's a compliment there george
hamilton
you're like you're like tang you're dry
and orange and no one has given up about
you since 1968.
hamilton
they're like a walking tumor
not exactly it's a big deal when you
spot a tumor
of course it wouldn't be a roast without
pizza lampanelli here everybody lisa
glampinelli good to see you lisa i've
never seen a circus bear in a pant suit
before
and you know what
lisa lisa seems she seems very confident
but she's actually not she's very sweet
she was telling me backstage that she
had knots in all four of her stomachs
the
you are you are one fat lady you you
have
you have more chins than a chinese fat
chick with tons of chins cause she's
because she's so fast and also
and
speaking of fact hulk hogan's here
everybody how about that
hulk i can't imagine why your wife left
you you're an old man who dresses like a
hooters waitress
keep keep your shirt on tits
you're 80. you had a reality show called
hogan knows best it should have been
called hogan grows breasts
sorry springer good to see you slithered
in here today uh springer you you
cultural sodomite you have
our civilization like gilbert's uncle on
valentine's day
you're an aide to bobby kennedy which
probably explains your connection to
hasselhoff i guess you like to hang
around guys whose careers end on a hotel
floor
you've done that's a good joke everybody
it's what we call roasting
anyway
i'm sorry if the meanness is piled up
but that's what we do here
and now on to the man of the happy hour
one more hand for the half everybody huh
david hasselhoff what a legend has hops
hassle off sitting on a lifeguard chair
cause that's what you're most known for
i guess when we roasted pam she should
have been sitting on a dick
where
that is that is quite a tuxedo you look
like adam lambert's prom date
you're
you're huge in europe you're even
knighted by the queen of england she
dubbed you cirrhosis of liver
household have you have you ever not
been drunk you used to have a car that
started when you talked to it now you
have a car that won't start when you
blow into it
you're such a drunk when alcohol does
its taxes it lists you as a dependent
you starred in checklist hyde on
broadway give him a round of applause
for that excellent acting
you played a guy you played a normal guy
who drinks something and then turns into
a raging abusive
what impressive range
baby
maybe for your next big leap you can go
out for the part of washed-up drunken
cheeseburger eater
hassle off you're drunk
you drink a lot right
your liver is so shriveled black and
dead if you put your ear to your side
you can hear it go what you're talking
about willis
you're
you're a good man you're a good dad
congratulations on being honored here
tonight i know you're taking a lot of
but uh but you're not gonna
remember any of it let's face it
thanks john stamos isn't he she great
[Applause]
john played the bongos in a beach boys
video wearing a pink tank top
[Music]
that couldn't have been any gayer if
george michaels was on your lap stuffing
crystal meth up your ass with rupert
everett's fist
you're on er now john congratulations
you're like susie esme's vagina you're
almost useless but somehow you keep
working
[Applause]
john was uh john was married to my
favorite supermodel rebecca romain
o'connell
jesus
oh
john you uh
john
you lost your wife to the fat kid from
stand by me
holy
look at you you greasy greek bastard i
look at you and i wonder how can there
be an energy crisis we shouldn't be
drilling in alaska we should be ringing
out your family's pillowcases
norm mcdonald is here one of the
funniest people ever norm's got a giant
gambling problem he's dropped more coin
in a casino than michael j fox at a
parking meter
it's a roast groaning grown
grown
brian posane look at him that giant
ghoul
we've all seen you shirtless on the
sarah silverman show it's hard to
believe you could be so out of shape
considering how often the townspeople
must chase you around with torches
the great cloris leachman of course is
here cloris leachman
flores is so old she lost her virginity
to a druid
what are you doing here cloris you're
the only person with any talent you've
won an oscar and nine emmys
when it comes to winning awards you've
been more voracious than john lovitz at
all the dick you can eat buffet
john lovetts you gay weeble
[Applause]
come on john there hasn't been a more
feminine jew in the closet since anne
frank
gilbert godfrey's here gilbert recently
had a baby
who would you you have the sex
appeal of a school bus fire
which brings me to the man of the hour
bob saget everybody huh bob sagan
bob
bob you are a genital wart on the
of american culture
seriously who gives a about bob
saget
with your long neck pointy beak and
granny glasses you're like the vlasic
pickle stork
except instead of delivering babies
you're not funny
[Applause]
you're like my seven-year-old son you
think cursing is hilarious and you're
not surprised your dick is the same size
it was in the first grade
[Applause]
and where the hell are the olsen twins
the olsens are like tom green's
testicles they look the same but one is
fake and empty inside and the other
one's been licked by heath ledger
he'd be cool with it
i read an interview where you refer to
yourself as an artist are you
kidding me
as an artist you use the phrase as an
artist you are a vortex of artistic
compromise charlie sheen watches you and
feels good about himself
you
you are an artist in the same way cloris
leachman is moist
you're not an artist bob and stop
enjoying your ironic hipness
that's going on with you these days
you're not cool
stop trying to be hip at one point in
your act you actually say who's your
daddy say my name look me in the eye
true that
holy i couldn't cringe any harder
if i watch my mom in a video
[Applause]
i'm done being mean bob i've met you a
bunch of times you've always been
hilarious and super cool and uh and
everybody that knows you loves and
respects you nobody ever has a bad thing
to say about you and uh that's that's
that's particularly surprising because
you're you're jewish
and you're obnoxious people thanks a lot
let me do this thanks thank you very
much everybody thanks a lot uh ron white
isn't he drunk everybody give him a hand
seriously
it looks like uh nick nolte let himself
go how about a hand
before i get to foxworthy specifically i
want to talk about all the blue-collar
guys these guys are like they're like
rock stars and by that i mean old and
boring and loaded with syphilis
the tour grows 15 million bucks 15
million you know this is at a time when
your fans have so many other
entertainment options
you know they they could have stayed
home and burned across or their sisters
or
you know i mean they had other choices
you know but
instead they got they got all gussied up
in their best who farted t-shirts and
they uh
they jump start the el camino and they
take the hard-earned money that they
made on an extra shift working to tilt
the world or rob in a liquor store
you know this is money they could have
spent on abortions or crystal meth and
they come out
they make an extra effort to come out
and see you guys
now
uh of uh speaking of abortions uh good
to see larry the cable guy here
jesus christ get her done
i saw larry at the beach because we hang
out at the beach me and larry
and i uh
from behind all you see are rolls of fat
and clumps and patches of hair
your back looks like lisa lampanelli's
seriously
good to see uh bill engvall here bill
he's a prolific bastard man he's got
seven comedy cds out without bill sears
would have no comedy section
seven cds bill did you ever think of
just saying something unfunny without
recording it
now uh
my friends from tough crowd are here of
course colin quinn and uh i noticed
recently blue collar tv took over tough
crowds time slot
and the network told colin that viewers
had a hard time understanding anything
he said
and uh so they replaced him with larry
the cable guy
now my my buddy nick apollo is here
and uh you know a lot of people say
nick's just a big dumb guinea
anyway on to our guest of honor
mr uh
mr jeff foxworthy folks uh
you know jeff has always been an
original and an innovator you know back
when everybody was doing corny
observational comedy jeff came up with
the idea of doing it in a southern
accent
very original a good twist
you are the comedy what wayne brady is
to black people
i've seen you dance you ever watch that
blue collar tv when he dances at the end
holy remember how ge smith how
he looked on saturday night live
you make him look like barishnikov on
ecstasy
you've always stayed cutting edge man
you really have uh with that keith
partridge haircut and that that ferret
growing on your lip
jesus that mustache should come with ass
chaps and a nipple ring
what are you thinking with your wardrobe
and that gay walrus mustache you look
like one of the village people on casual
friday
you look like a guy tonya harding would
in a 78 nova
you put out 11 books including a
cookbook you got greeting cards and slot
machines you're like the redneck martha
stewart with a smaller
you are a billionaire you're like donald
trump without the funny tv show
seriously jeff though you're a giant
comedy star you deserve your success and
uh and look you made enough money that
you don't have to live in the south but
you choose to
so you're uh you're you're the real deal
congratulations
you look like ronald mcdonald
ball's corpse then pushed it down a
flight of stairs
holy
what's with all the surgery kathy lord
you've been stitched up thousands of
times but you're still sad to look at
you like the aids quilt
what a night a couple of trolls a fairy
and a giant all going after a
sunken-eyed little monster who's
obsessed with jewelry it's like the lord
of the rings
the great carl reiner is here this is
very exciting yes
carl
you
are such a comedy icon that joan named
one of those shitty watches she sells on
qvc after you it's uh it's the carl
reiner edition it's got liver spotted
hands and it's running out of time
mario cantone is here
mario
you are one tiny loudmouth fairy
your father must have been devastated
when you came out of the cupboard
brad garrett from everybody loves
raymond huh holy
you are a monster brad how'd you
ever get your head so far up ray
romano's ass with those bolts in your
neck
and
whitney whitney cummings is here for
some reason
i guess uh i guess since kathy and joan
have huge gay followings we needed
someone with no following
whitney
whitney's a girl who obviously knows the
answer to the question hey who do you
have to blow to get on one of these
roasts
and speaking of degrading yourself
sexually to get ahead in show business
tom arnold is here
tom
it is great you could take time out from
being roseanne's ex-husband to be here
tom you twitchy spazz
joan
actually named
another one of her shitty watches after
you too
it's the tom arnold that never stops
ticking and used to come in a giant
hairy box
and
finally
finally we get to comedy legend an
irritating jewish lady gilbert godfried
is here everybody huh
gilbert
holy gilbert you look like you
smell like pee
and
gilbert's famously cheap uh i'm
impressed you're here gilbert you know
because uh you know when you do these
things you got to buy new clothes you
got to take a week off from work but you
showed up you tightened your belt and
you came you're like david carradine
and
yes a sympathetic figure if ever there
was one
and now it really is my honor to talk
about comedy great joan rivers joan
rivers everybody
this is exciting
joan
you are one irritating jew broad the
first time i heard your voice my
foreskin fell off
what have you done to your upper lip did
you blow a beehive
holy you look like steve and tyler
the life raft
seriously you're not the only one here
all these rubber-faced monsters what the
what what what goes into people's heads
out here why did you really
really is that
good
how much worse could your real face look
than that clown mask you've had welded
on your head you
you used to look your age now you don't
even look your species
you
you once said you succeeded by saying
what everyone else is thinking and
that's not true it's not true i never
heard you say holy what the
did i do to my face
i look like a surprised catfish
joan you really are an absolutely
incredible uh talent you're absolutely
hysterical every comic i know respects
you that's a god's honest truth everyone
thinks you're hilarious i think you're
the best and at your age you're still
relevant still cool and uh you even
got a boob job just a few years ago
you're every man's dream and and by that
i mean every man that dreams of titty
a crocodile
thank you almost congratulations joe
thank you pillsbury jew boy
jason that was a that was a refreshing
change these days the only time you're
funny is on a rerun
you've done uh you've really tried to
hang in there after seinfeld you had
shows like bob patterson and listen up
those shows disappeared faster than a
bowl of percocet at farrah fawcett's
house
[Applause]
you've been in more turds than andy
dick's penis
[Applause]
look at his deus
fat guys old ladies and an asian i feel
like i'm on a bus to atlantic city
[Applause]
look at this michelle nichols farrah
fawcett and betty white uh i'll take
women i would masturbate to 30 years ago
for a thousand alex
what a cruel joke three women you'd want
to 30 years ago and one i wouldn't
30 beers from now
already laying him
you
you fat drunk slob
already your liver has more holes in it
than mel gibson's apology
you're out
your liver's so black lisa lempinelli
tried to get it to her up the ass
and never call again
[Applause]
artie your pal george takei is here
sorry to pick on you george i know it
couldn't be easy
uh being a gay japanese man in the 50s i
mean it it had to be almost impossible
to pronounce glory hole with a japanese
accent
[Applause]
to our guest of honor now the great uh
the great william shatner everybody
bill it's uh
that was that was quite an entrance when
i when i heard someone was gonna come on
a horse i uh
i thought wow the network's really gonna
let andy dick and lisa lampanelli get
away with murder but
[Applause]
bill uh you're not just uh brilliant and
old and fat you're
you're an inspiration uh you prove that
having no talent can be seen as hip and
ironic
you overact more than betty white's
bladder
wow
then
uh and of course there was tj hooker the
only thing i remember about that show
was your hair and that hot chick what's
her face adrian's a med
what uh
what happened to her
you're a uh you're a humanitarian you
work with a foundation to bring peace to
the middle east and uh whatever it is
you're doing keep it up
because it's uh
it's really working
you know uh
the one of the most surreal parts of
this business is that i get to stand
here and make fun of of a legend like
you you're an enormous part of my youth
and you made captain kirk larger than
life and really honestly no actor who's
ever lived could have could have done
more with that role and uh and the fact
that you you continue to crank out the
best work you've done today when
statistically you you should be dead is
is really really inspiring thank you
very much
thank everybody jimmy kimmel isn't he
doughy
really
isn't he isn't he about to be canceled
keep it going for uh for jimmy kimmel
wow that was that was great jim i've
never seen you be funny on tv before
jimmy how the hell is that show still on
the air
that was that wasn't a premise to a joke
that was a real question
i don't want to say nobody watches it
but more people have seen dennis rodman
reading
by the way
pam
kid kid rock wanted to be here but he
got stuck in a 20 year old
corolla
look at you you horse-toothed bastard
corolla you got a mouth full of
two-by-fours every
every time you smile i remember to
waterproof my deck
corolla's an italian word it means one
eyebrow
the love lines
only in america what a crappy show the
love lines is
yeah teenagers calling in to complain
about their abortions and their anal
warts
it's like listening to the messages on
andy dick's answering machine
now uh
speaking uh speaking of anal warts uh
good to see courtney love here
[Applause]
courtney uh what the hell happened to
you you had a great band you're a very
talented actress and your career dried
up faster than sarah silverman's
around guys who can't help her in the
business
[Applause]
good to see uh eddie griffin of course
eddie griffin people said there wouldn't
be any big movie stars here tonight and
they were right
uh
tommy lee of course it's tough to slam a
guy for having a huge but
we've all seen a sex take tommy and i
know the camera adds five inches but
jesus
your is so huge i had to fast
forward to tape to see all of it
my five-year-old son walked in as i was
watching it great now i got to explain
why the pretty blonde girl is being
stabbed with the harpoon
[Applause]
of course uh this brings me to pam
the beautiful goddess hi pam
pam uh pam i i love you pam i've been a
fan of yours for so long but i gotta say
watching you in that sex tape was like a
whole new experience for me uh because
up until then i'd never seen anyone get
gonorrhea before
that that was weird
you're a vegetarian but you have no
trouble swallowing a moose
you're environmentally conscious but
you've caused more seed to be spilled in
the department of agriculture
i've been a fan of yours for so long and
i i feel terrible that you're gonna get
abused here today who are these nobodies
who are these nobodies up here to make
fun of you people like lisa lampanelli
i'm sure she's going to come up here and
be mean and fat
and
but you know what but you know what
her
you've been on the cover of playboy so
many times and you didn't have to
hugh hefner to do it
you them anyway but you didn't
have to
that's right you didn't have to
you're multi-talented you have a tv show
you're involved in lots of humanitarian
causes you've even written two novels
you're busier than courtney's pharmacist
what
what's with the books pam you have two
novels out two novels you've now written
more books than you've read
i
i love your show stacked it shows your
range and it proves to everyone that you
can masturbate to a sitcom no matter how
unfunny it is
i love it stacked you get it it's a
double entendre
yeah you work in a bookstore there's
stacks there and you're stacked so we
call it stacked
that's hilarious
i love that okay here's the idea guys
she she she works in a jewelry store and
we call it pearl necklace what do you
think
you starting in a show about books and
reading is like tom cruise starring in a
show about vaginas
all right
now uh
now
i will say this pam i am seriously a
giant fan of yours and uh you know we're
gonna make fun of you a lot here but to
get to the level you've gotten is true
genius it really is absolute genius
people cannot help but love you
people can't help but love you you got
unbelievable talent and you're america's
sweetheart you're a canadian but those
tits were made in america thank you very
much
thank you everybody keep it going for
cat williams everybody isn't he adorable
what a cute little kind of person he is
holy cat you're like afro sheen
some white people have heard of you but
no one knows what you do
what a teeny little pimp
man being a pimp ain't easy especially
when you got to stand on phone books to
smack a
[Applause]
this is great cat williams flame of
flame snoop iced tea there's so many
black dicks up here i feel like we're
doing this roast in lisa lampanelli's
mouth
[Applause]
iced tea is here holy iced tea you
fossil
holy you're so old the first thing
you bought with your record deal money
was your freedom
[Applause]
on your first album the n word was negro
some more is here
some more when it comes to movies maybe
you should do some less
soul plane holy
that was such a horrible embarrassment
to black people bridget nielsen tried to
it
[Applause]
bridget nielsen's here good to see you
sitting up sweetheart
i uh
i guess you're in rehab and i i really i
really hope that works out for you but
uh but seriously if you want to stop
repeating the disgusting things you've
done in the past why don't you just get
your puppy sewn shut
your puppy's so big sylvester stallone
left his career in there
[Applause]
god you are a big ghoulish
woman i'm talking to you carrot top
[Applause]
jesus
what happened to your face
good to see snoop here snooper
snoop smokes so much hemp he wants
a rope
snoop you're filled with toxins you've
killed people and you've been banned
from every country on the planet you're
like chinese toothpaste
[Laughter]
and now uh
guestamon or flava flav this is really
this exciting flavor it really is
this is an honor
i've uh i've never roasted an oily
cadaver before you're like a turd with
teeth look at yourself
i love the crown you look like king lear
got trapped in a forest fire
you are one black mother
you're like a skeleton wrapped in
electrical tape
you look like edie amin after a
three-year crack binge on the sun
all right flame well you're the best man
you're one of the most memorable people
ever in the history of entertainment and
i love the viking helmet i guess
bridget's not the only big cold
scandinavian thing you've stuck your
head into
thank you everybody
[Music]
bye